Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Football programs, jerseys, 1933-1990; RG0054 Series 36; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 4, Box 2, Box 1)
  - GWU Athletic Review, 11/07/1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Football program, George Washington vs. Bucknell, Nov. 7, 1952. Folder also includes game statistics.
  - GWU Athletic Review, 11/14/1952 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Football program, George Washington vs. Davidson, Nov. 14, 1952. Folder also includes game statistics and press pass for game issued by GW.
  - GWU Athletic Review, 11/04/1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    2 football programs, George Washington vs. West Virginia, Nov. 4, 1955. Folder also includes game statistics and West Virginia marching band pre-game program (with diagrams).
  - Rowing jersey, 1980 ca. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Possible rowing jersey, white with blue across the middle.
  - Cross country jersey, 1990 ca. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Cross country jersey, blue and white with yellow strip across the middle.
  - Rowing jersey, 1980 ca. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Rowing jersey, blue and white with "GW" stencil.
  - Basketball jersey, 1956ca. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Basketball jersey of Joe Holup, class of 1956. Gold with blue lettering, number 16 between "George" and "Washington."
  - Basketball jersey, 1956ca. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Basketball jersey of Joe Holup, class of 1956. Cream ("buff") with blue lettering, number 16 between "George" and "Washington."
  - Football jersey, 1933, 1933 ca. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    GW football jersey, number 20, ca. 1933. This textile has blue sleeves with red and cream stripes (refered to as "hard jersey" style in the football programs). This applique style jersey consists of a number 20 sown onto a cream colored background and red stripes along the bottom portion. Also attached to the bottom edge of this jersey, are buttons which would enclose the front and back of the uniform. This jersey is believed to have belonged to football player Benedict Plotnicki (#20 in 1933). By 1935 this style jersey was retired. Originally on exhibit in the David S. Brown Memorabilia Room.
- Athletics files, 1890-2004; RG0054 Series 37; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 13)
  This series contains information regarding the history of the athletics department at GW.
  Former Vertical Files
  - Smith Center, 12/02/1972-2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Smith Center - naming ceremony 10/2/73, 12/02/1972-12/06/1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Smith Center - summer programs, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Sports, 02/02/1954-2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Sports - awards luncheons/awards, 1931-2004, 05/13/1931-05/03/2004 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Sports - cheerleading/spirit, 11/23/1934-1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Sports - fall sports schedule, 1972-09/1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Sports - GW Athletic Hall of Fame, 1960-02/14/2003 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Sports - GW Athletic Hall of Fame - Auerbach, Red, 06/09/1998-03/22/2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Sports - history, 09/14/1925-02/2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Sports - intramural/extramural program, 1963-1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Sports - mascots, 1965-03/2004 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sports - NCAA, 02/1987-05/27/1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Sports - newsletters - Coach's Corner, 10/17/1955-09/18/1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Sports - spring sports schedules, 1953-1990 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Sports - Student Athlete Handbook, 1987, 1997, 1987-1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Sports - men's athletics - baseball, 1974-05/19/2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sports - summer programs, 06/20/1977-07/29/1994 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball, 1971-2005 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball - coaches - Gimelstob, Gerry, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball - coaches - Jarvis, Mike, 04/14/1997-07/03/1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball - coaches - Kuester, John, 1985-03/05/2004 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball - history, 1941-1996 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball - newsletters, 09/1971-2003 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Sports - men's athletics - basketball - programs, 1913-2002 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Sports - men's athletics - crew, 1973-2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - coaches - Camp, Jim, 08/1963-1966 -- --ca. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - compiled record, 1890-1966, 1890-1966 -- --ca. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - history, 1931-1965 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - history - 1890-1950, 1925-02/01/1985 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - history - 1951-1967, 1953-1965 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - history - abolition of program, 1967, 07/27/1987 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - players - Leemans, Tuffy, 02/03/1978-05/15/2001 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - programs, 1907, 1920, 11/1907-1920 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - scouting reports, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Sports - men's athletics - football - soccer, 1971-1988 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Sports - men's athletics - swimming and diving, 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Sports - men's athletics - track and field - programs, 1911-1917, 02/04/1911-03/02/1917 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Sports - men's athletics - wrestling, 1977-1989 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports, 1975-1988 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - badminton, 02/14/1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - basketball, 1976-1999 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - basketball - coaches, 06/16/1981-06/30/1988 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - basketball - history, 10/19/1978-1994 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - basketball - players, 1982-1995 -- --ca. (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - basketball - tournaments, 12/05/1986-1995 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - Colonial Women, 1978-1987 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - Colonial Women - newsletter - Communique, 1984-1988, 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - gymnastics, 08/04/1974-1990 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - history, 1954-1984 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - history - Title IX, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - intramural programs, 1947-1982 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - publications - The Changing Scene in Women's Athletics, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - publications - The Colonial Women In Action, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - publications - GW Women's Athletics, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - racquet sports, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - rifle team, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - soccer, 1980-1989 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - swimming and diving, 04/26/1955-1987 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - tennis, 1977-1989 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - volleyball, 1977-1994 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Sports - women's athletics & sports - women's sports schedule, 1976-1989 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Videotapes, Audiotapes, and Film, 1973-2003; RG0054 Series 38; 17.5 Linear feet (Box 11, Box 9, Box 10, Box 6, Box 7, Box 12, Box 4, Box 8, Box 5, Box 2, Box 1, Box 3, Box 13)
  This series contains video tapes (VHS, Betacam SP, u-matic) audio tapes, and film from the GW athletic department. These tapes highlight various sports teams and events.
  - Men's Basketball, 12/22/1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    G.W. Basketball-South Carolina 12-22-86 GWG #1
  - Men's Basketball, 12/29/1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    G.W. Basketball-Tape #1 12-29-86 - Jacksonville
  - Men's Basketball, 12/29/1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball, 02/25/1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Aircheck GW-Rutgers 2/25/87
  - Men's Basketball, 02/25/1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Halftime interview for GW-Rutgers game, Feb. 25, 1987
  - Men's Basketball, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    George Washington (WRC) 1987
  - Men's Basketball, 01/15/1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    A10 Men's Basketball 1-15-89 Temple @ GWU
  - Men's Basketball, 01/17/1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    A10 Men's Basketball 1-17-89 WVU @ GWU
  - Men's Basketball, 05/22/1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    NCAA Press Conference May 22, 1989
  - Men's Basketball, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    GW Men's Basketball Stills 89
  - Men's Basketball, 11/20/1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    11-20-90 G.W. Basketball vs. Soviets Tape #1
  - Men's Basketball, 12/11/1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    B-Ball vs. UMBC 12/11/90 #4
  - Men's Basketball, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    GW 90-91 Features
  - Men's Basketball, 01/15/1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    UMASS vs. GW WWLPTV 1/15/91
  - Men's Basketball, 01/17/1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    GW vs. Rutgers 1/17/91 Tape #2 of 5
  - Men's Basketball, 01/17/1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    GW vs. Rutgers 1/17/91 Tape #3 of 5
  - Men's Basketball, 01/26/1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1/26/91 Tape #2 GW Men's B-Ball U-MASS Regular Play
  - Men's Basketball, 01/26/1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    1/26/91 Tape #3 GW Men's B-Ball U-MASS 2nd Half Regular Play
  - Men's Basketball, 01/26/1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    1/26/91 Tape #2 GW Men's B-Ball University of Massachusetts 2nd Half
  - Men's Basketball, 01/26/1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    1/21/91 Tape 1 of 1 GW Coaches Show (St. Bonaventure close)
  - Men's Basketball, 02/23/1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    American @ GWU 2/23/91
  - Men's Basketball, 03/07/1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    GW/Penn ST. Mar 07 1991 #1 ESPN
  - Men's Basketball, 11/18/1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    B-Ball 11/18/91 #1 CAM 6 (Martin)
  - Men's Basketball, 11/18/1991 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    B-Ball 11/18/91 #2 CAM 6 (Martin)
  - Men's Basketball, 01/07/1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Coaches Corner: George Washington University 1/7/92 Tape #1
  - Men's Basketball, 01/07/1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Childhelp, 03/05/1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Public Service Announcement. Audio master with low res pix.
  - Men's Basketball, 01/18/1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    1-18-92 Rutgers @ GW 1 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 01/18/1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1-18-92 Rutgers @ GW 2 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 02/01/1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    GWTV GW v. St. Joseph's Tape 1 1st Half 2/1/92
  - Men's Basketball, 02/01/1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    GWTV GW v. St. Joseph's Tape 2 1st Half 2/1/92
  - Men's Basketball, 02/01/1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    GWTV GW v. St. Joseph's Tape 3 1st Half 2/1/92
  - Men's Basketball, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    1992 GWU Basketball Team Headshots
  - Men's Basketball, 11/02/1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Rodney Palletson/Chris Knolhe 11/2/92
  - Men's Basketball, 01/06/1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Men's Basketball 1/6/93 GW at James Madison Home Team Sports
  - Men's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    The George Washington University 1992-93 Men's Basketball Video Yearbook WRC-TV Channel 4
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    1993-1994 GW Men's Basketball Hilites
  - Men's Basketball, 01/16/1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    1-16-93 GWU @ UMASS 1 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 01/16/1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    1-16-93 GWU @ UMASS 2 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 02/13/1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    M-B-Ball 2/13/93 UMASS at GWU 1 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 02/13/1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    M-B-Ball 2/13/93 UMASS at GWU 2 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 02/15/1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    2/15/93 Richmond at GWU 1 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 02/15/1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    2/15/93 Richmond at GWU 2 of 2
  - Men's Basketball, 02/21/1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Feb 21 '93 WVA at GWU 1st Half
  - Men's Basketball, 02/21/1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    WVA at GWU Feb 21 '93 2nd Half
  - Men's Basketball, 03/22/1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    George Washington Univ. 3/22/93
  - Men's Basketball, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    1993 Basketball Interviews
  - Men's Basketball, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Team Reaction to '93 NCAA MBB Tourn.
  - Men's Basketball, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    GWU Men's Basketball Headshots 93-94
  - Men's Basketball, 02/25/1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    George Washington University Men's Basketball head shots 93-94 season
  - Men's Basketball, 02/25/1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Africa World Tonight 2/25/94 GWU Dare/Stearns
  - Men's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    The George Washington University 1994-95 Men's Basketball Team Season Highlights
  - Men's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    GWU Men's B-Ball '94-'95 Headshots
  - Men's Basketball, 02/28/1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    GW vs. Rutgers 2/28/95 Tape #1
  - Men's Basketball, 02/28/1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    GW vs. Rutgers 2/28/95 Tape #2
  - Men's Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    1995-96 George Washington Colonials Men's Basketball
  - Men's Basketball, 02/26/1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    GW men's basketball 1995-1996 at Xavier 2/26/96
  - Men's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    1996-97 George Washington Men's Basketball Highlight Video
  - Men's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    1997-98 Basketball Highlights and International Piece
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    1997-98 GW Men's Basketball Highlight Tape
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball, 02/07/1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    GW vs. St. Joe's 2/7/98 copy
  - Men's Basketball, 02/09/1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    GW B-Ball story on channel 5 Monday Feb. 9, 1998
  - Men's Basketball, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    1998 GWU Men's Basketball Team
  - Men's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    1998-99 George Washington Men's Basketball Highlight Video
  - Men's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Men's Basketball, 01/04/1999 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    A Conversation With Brian "A Night At The Game GW vs. Ohio 1/4/99
  - Men's Basketball, 02/24/1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Goin' Deep 2/24/99 GW's International Players
  - Men's Basketball, 03/31/1999 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Shawnta Rogers Feature More Than A Game 3/31/99
  - Men's Basketball, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    1999 Final Four Men's Basketball
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    1999-2000 George Washington Men's Basketball Highlights
  - Men's Basketball, 03/09/2001 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Atlantic 10 Television Network Temple vs. George Washington 3/9/01
  - Men's Basketball, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    2001-2002 George Washington University Men's Basketball Headshots
  - Men's Basketball, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    2002 George Washington Men's Basketball Highlight Tape
  - Men's Basketball, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Men's Basketball, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    2002-2003 George Washington Men's Basketball Headshots
  - Men's Basketball, 01/25/2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Atlantic 10 Television Network Massachusetts @ George Washington 1/25/03
  - Men's Basketball, 02/16/2004 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Pops Mensah-Bonsu Feature 2-16-04 NBC4 Sports
  - Men's Basketball, 02/16/2004 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Men's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    2004-2005 Men's Basketball Highlights Video
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Dirkk Sules Tape
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    GW vs. Duquesne TV Tape
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    12/4 GW vs. Hartford Tape 1
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    12/4 GW vs. Hartford Tape #3
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    GW vs. MD
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    GW vs. UMBC #3
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    GW Foreign players
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    A-10 Media Day
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Men's Basketball
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Midnight Madness B-Ball Excerpts
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    GW Basketball WUSA Ch 9
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Temple-GW Highlights ODU-GW Highlights #5
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    GW Basketball (Men's)
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 1970 ca. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    GWU on TV CBS (Women's Basketball 1970s)
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 01/17/1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    GW Women's Basketball 1/17/91
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 01/21/1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    GW Women's Basketball GW vs. Penn State 1/21/91 Tape #2
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 02/09/1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    9 Feb. 91 #1 GW Women's B-B George Mascot
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 02/09/1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    9 Feb. 91 #2 GW Women Mascot Interview Alumni
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 02/28/1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    GW Women vs. Penn State 2/28/91
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 11/29/1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    GW vs. Texas Women's Basketball UNLV/7-Up Desert Classic Nov. 29, 1991 Tape 1 of 2
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 11/29/1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    GW vs. Texas Women's Basketball UNLV/7-Up Desert Classic Nov. 29, 1991 Tape 2 of 2
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 11/30/1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Stanford vs. GW Tape #1 11/30/91 Women's Basketball UNLV/7-Up Desert Classic
  - Men's Basketball/Women's Basketball, 11/30/1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Stanford vs. GW Tape #2 11/30/91 Women's Basketball UNLV/7-Up Desert Classic
  - Women's Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    1991-92 Pac-10 Women's Basketball Preview
  - Women's Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    1991-1992 Women's Basketball
  - Women's Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    1991-1992 GW WBB vs. Texas
  - Women's Basketball, 02/11/1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    NCAA Spotlight on Women's Basketball 2/11/92 Joe McKeon and Jennifer Shasky Tape 1 of 2
  - Women's Basketball, 02/11/1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    NCAA Spotlight on Women's Basketball 2/11/92 Joe McKeon and Jennifer Shasky Tape 2 of 2
  - Women's Basketball, 09/1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Media Seminar GW 9-92 WBB
  - Women's Basketball, 02/01/1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Atlantic 10 Championship 1st Half Women's Basketball vs. Rutgers 2/1/92
  - Women's Basketball, 02/01/1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Atlantic 10 Championship 2nd Half Women's Basketball vs. Rutgers 2/1/92
  - Women's Basketball, 11/23/1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    GW Women's Basketball Headshots 11/23/92
  - Women's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    GW Women Hilite Tape 1992-93
  - Women's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    GW Women's Basketball Highlight Video 1992-93
  - Women's Basketball, 02/25/1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Women's Basketball-George Washington at Temple 2/25/93
  - Women's Basketball, 03/06/1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    1st Half 3/6/93 GW vs. RU Women
  - Women's Basketball, 03/06/1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    2nd Half 3/6/93 GW vs. RU Women
  - Women's Basketball, 12/20/1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    GWU vs. Vanderbilt Women's B-ball Tape 1 of 5 12/20/93
  - Women's Basketball, 12/20/1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    GWU vs. Vanderbilt Women's B-ball Tape 2 of 5 12/20/93
  - Women's Basketball, 12/20/1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    GWU vs. Vanderbilt Women's B-ball Tape 3 of 5 12/20/93
  - Women's Basketball, 12/20/1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    GWU vs. Vanderbilt Women's B-ball Tape 4 of 5 12/20/93
  - Women's Basketball, 12/20/1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    GWU vs. Vanderbilt Women's B-ball Tape 5 of 5 12/20/93
  - Women's Basketball, 12/22/1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    GW Women's NCAA bid 12/22/93
  - Women's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    1993-1994 GW Women's Basketball Hilites
  - Women's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Women's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball, 02/13/1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    A-10 2/13/93 WVU @ GWU Women's Low Angle Hilites
  - Women's Basketball, 10/1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    1993-94 GW Women's Head shots October 1993
  - Women's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    George Washington University Women's Basketball Headshots 93-94 season
  - Women's Basketball, 01/15/1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    GWU vs. West VA Women's B-ball Tape 1 of 4 1/15/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/15/1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    GWU vs. West VA Women's B-ball Tape 2 of 4 1/15/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/15/1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    GWU vs. West VA Women's B-ball Tape 3 of 4 1/15/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/15/1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    GWU vs. West VA Women's B-ball Tape 4 of 4 1/15/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/29/1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    GWU vs. Rutgers Women's B-ball Tape 1 of 5 1/29/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/29/1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    GWU vs. Rutgers Women's B-ball Tape 2 of 5 1/29/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/29/1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    GWU vs. Rutgers Women's B-ball Tape 3 of 5 1/29/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/29/1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    GWU vs. Rutgers Women's B-ball Tape 4 of 5 1/29/94
  - Women's Basketball, 01/29/1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    GWU vs. Rutgers Women's B-ball Tape 5 of 5 1/29/94
  - Women's Basketball, 02/19/1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    GWU vs. St. Joseph's Women's B-ball Tape 1 of 4 2/19/94
  - Women's Basketball, 02/19/1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    GWU vs. St. Joseph's Women's B-ball Tape 2 of 4 2/19/94
  - Women's Basketball, 02/19/1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    GWU vs. St. Joseph's Women's B-ball Tape 3 of 4 2/19/94
  - Women's Basketball, 02/19/1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    GWU vs. St. Joseph's Women's B-ball Tape 4 of 4 2/19/94
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    GWU Women's B-Ball '94-'95 Headshots
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    1994-1995 Women's Basketball Postseason Honors
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    "The George Washington University 1994-95 Women's Basketball Team Sweet Sixteen"
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Women's Basketball, 01/15/1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    GW-UMass Women's Basketball January 15, 1995 Home Team Sports Tape 1 of 2
  - Women's Basketball, 01/15/1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    GW-UMass Women's Basketball January 15, 1995 Home Team Sports Tape 2 of 2
  - Women's Basketball, 01/22/1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)